<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ux on Julian Gaviria — Web Designer</title>
    <link>https://julian.is/categories/ux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ux on Julian Gaviria — Web Designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://julian.is/categories/ux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Web Apps — The Next Step in Responsive Web Design</title>
      <link>https://julian.is/article/progressive-web-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julian.is/article/progressive-web-apps/</guid>
      <description>Late last week, Smashing Magazine, one of the largest and most influential online publications for web design, posted on Facebook that their website was “now running as a Progressive Web App.”
 Honestly, I didn’t think much of it. Progressive Web Apps are for the hardcore web application developers creating the next online cloud-based Photoshop (complicated stuff), right? I scrolled on and went about my day.
Then, I saw CSS wizard, Harry Roberts, tweet about making some setting changes in CloudFlare and achieving the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User-Friendly Exit Intent Modals</title>
      <link>https://julian.is/article/exit-intent-popups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julian.is/article/exit-intent-popups/</guid>
      <description>As users, we hate popups. We never click on them. They’re annoying. They get in the way. But as conversion rate optimizers, they just work. They produce results by making themselves very difficult to ignore, and believe it or not, people do convert on these. Good news, though — somewhere, somehow, someone was able to find a middle ground to this. It’s what we call “exit intent modals” or, if you prefer to sound Google smart, “exit intent interstitials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growth-Driven Design Case Study</title>
      <link>https://julian.is/article/conversion-rate-optimization-case-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julian.is/article/conversion-rate-optimization-case-study/</guid>
      <description>Over the past year, we at Results-Powered Marketing (the agency I work for) have integrated Growth-Driven Design into our approach to building and maintaining websites. For those unfamiliar, GDD is an agile approach applied to the website development process — the goal is to get something out the door as soon as possible, test, iterate, and keep making tweaks to drive better and stronger results for our clients.
In this specific case study, we were able to increase our client&amp;rsquo;s new monthly leads generated by 278%.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>